<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SeeYa</string>

    <string name="login_greet">
        Welcome to SeeYa! Here you can find and attend events or meet new people and have fun!
    </string>

    <string name="register_title_step_1">
        Welcome! Start creating an account by entering your email!
    </string>

    <string name="register_title_step_2">
        Now come up with a strong password!
    </string>

    <string name="register_title_step_3">
        Now onto your details, I guess you have a name? Unless you don\'t…for some reason
    </string>

    <string name="register_title_step_5">
        Cool! You have a name! Now would you like to choose a profile picture?
    </string>

    <string name="register_title_step_4">
        What about your interests? (Mandatory btw)
    </string>

    <string name="register_title_step_6">
        Check your email, and enter the code we sent you!
    </string>

    <string name="event_category_meetup_subtitle">
        Casual gatherings to hang out, share interests, or just have a good time together.
    </string>
    <string name="event_category_live_show_subtitle">
        Public events like concerts, stand-ups, and performances, usually with tickets.
    </string>
    <string name="event_category_online_subtitle">
        Virtual events such as game nights, discussions, or watch parties you can join from anywhere.
    </string>
    <string name="event_category_networking_subtitle">
        Opportunities to meet new people, exchange ideas, or volunteer and grow your circle.
    </string>


    <!-- EVENT TYPES ( OPEN & CLOSED ) -->
    <string name="event_type_open_description">
        Anyone can join this event without an invitation or approval.
    </string>

    <string name="event_type_closed_description">
        Only approved members can join this event; an invitation or organizer’s approval is required.
    </string>

    <!-- Club Categories Description-->
    <string name="club_category_subtitle_community">
        Connect with like-minded people, share your interests, and just have a good time together.
    </string>
    <string name="club_category_subtitle_volunteering">
        Make a difference together: help out, support others, and spread some good energy.
    </string>
    <string name="club_category_subtitle_networking">
        Meet new people, grow your connections, and level up in your professional journey.
    </string>
    <string name="club_category_subtitle_promotion">
        Share your projects, art, or business and get the spotlight you deserve.
    </string>
</resources>